×

_menu_

[

**Penana**](https://www.penana.com/home.php)

_search_

_search_ 

Popular Tags

What Others Are Reading

Login_arrow\_drop\_down_

Email _email_ 

Password _lock_ 

 Remember me

OR  
  Login with Facebook

Register_arrow\_drop\_down_

Pen Name _edit_ 

Email _email_ 

Password _lock_ 

   I have read, understand, and agree to the Penana [Terms of Service](https://www.penana.com/terms.php). 

OR  
  Login with Facebook

Please use Chrome or Firefox for better user experience!

_menu_

* * Discover

    *   Stories

    *   Short pieces

    *   Contests

    *   Charts

    * Me
        
    *   Write
        
    *   Society
        
    *   Hub

    [Privacy](https://www.penana.com/privacy.php) · [Terms](https://www.penana.com/terms.php) · [FAQ](https://www.penana.com/faq.php) · [Feedback](https://www.penana.com/feedback.php)  
    _language_Language settings · [Mobile view](https://m.penana.com/privacy?v=mobile)  
    
    Penana © 2024

Privacy Policy
==============

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully.

**Our Pledge:**

We pledge to meet fully, and where possible exceed, in complying with the requirements of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Chapter 486 of the Laws of Hong Kong). In doing so, we will ensure compliance by our staff with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality.

**Types of Personal Information Collected**

Personal information means any information that is related to an identified person, or that may be used to identify an individual. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data).

For the purpose of carrying on our business, including registration and administration of our website and related products and services (including relevant online services), we may collect, use, store and transfer different kinds of personal data which we have grouped together as follows:

* Identity Data includes first name, last name, username or similar identifier, marital status, title, date of birth and gender.
* Contact Data includes billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers.
* Financial Data includes bank account and payment card details.
* Transaction Data includes details about payments to and from you and other details of products and services you have purchased from us.
T* echnical Data includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this website.
* Profile Data includes your username and password, purchases or orders made by you, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses, education and profession; hobbies and leisure activities; Other related products and services subscribed to; and Family and household demographics.
* Usage Data includes information about how you use our website, products and services.
* Marketing and Communications Data includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.

**How We Use Your Information**

We uses the collected data for various purposes such as:

* to allow you to sign in to your account
* to allow you to interact with other users
* to process payments and payouts
* to send merchandise to your shipping address
* to send you emails relevant to your usage, as controlled by your email preferences
* to send you emails that may interest you, as controlled by your email preferences
* to reply to your questions
* to provide to you existing and enhanced services related to your Penana account
* to verify your identity to comply with applicable laws
* to promote your Penana account for greater discoverability
* to understand how you use the service and create better tools for users
* to conduct research and development to improve Penana and develop future products
* to prevent fraud and abuse on Penana
* in any other way we may describe when you provide the information;
* for any other purpose with your consent.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Penana discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Penana’s behalf or to provide services available at Penana’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Penana’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. In addition, in some cases we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Penana or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Penana goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Penana may continue to use your personal and non-personal information only as set forth in this policy. Otherwise, Penana will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors, service providers and affiliated organizations, as described above, Penana discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Penana believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Penana, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Penana website and have supplied your email address, Penana may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Penana and its products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Penana takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

You should also be aware that some elements of User Information are made available to other users (e.g., if you publish information to your public profile). If you submit information to our web site such as “stories”, “comments”, “discussion” or “idea exchange”, such information will be visible to other users, meaning that you lose any privacy rights you might have with regards to that information. Such disclosures may also increase your chances of receiving unwanted communications.

**Cookies**

A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your system. To use portions of Penana's website you must set your browser to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. Some of our business partners (e.g., service providers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.penana.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertiser or other third parties.

**Data Quality**

We will take reasonable steps to insure that all data collected is accurate, complete and timely for the purposes for which they are to be used. We urge you to check your profile regularly to insure that such information is accurate, complete and timely. If you wish to get your data deleted from our records, please send a mail to [\[email protected\]](https://www.penana.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

**Account deletion**

Upon your request to [terminate your account](https://www.penana.com/delete_account), we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, some information may be retained in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with legal requirements.

**Third Party Sites**

Penana's website contains links to other sites. When you click on one of these links you are being transferred to a website operated by someone other than Penana, and the operator of that website may have a different privacy policy. Penana does not share your personal information with these websites and is not responsible for their individual privacy practices. We encourage you to investigate the privacy policies of these operators.

**Future Changes**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we have outlined in this Privacy Policy and to our [Terms of Service Policy](https://www.penana.com/terms.php). Penana may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy.

**Oversight and Questions**

We welcome comments and questions on this policy. As stated above, we are dedicated to protecting your privacy, and we will make every reasonable effort to keep your information secure. Questions regarding our policy should be directed via e-mail ([\[email protected\]](https://www.penana.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection))

Penana reserves the right to change these terms and conditions at any time without prior notice. Penana reserves the right to make the final decision in case of any disputes.

Updated May 2022

##### 

REGISTER

      I have read, understand, and agree to the Penana [Terms of Service](https://www.penana.com/terms.php). 

##### 

LOGIN

    Remember Me  

OR

Login with Facebook

×

Subscribe

Go to the magazine

/

\+ Add tip

The tip will be charged every payment period

\+ Add promotion code

Apply _close_

* * *

Recipient Name

Shipping address

Phone Number

 I prefer **not to receive** the physical benefits.  

Pay with

 xxxx xxxx xxxx

This is a one-time purchase.

If you don't cancel before the trial ends, you will automatically be charged the subscription fee every until you cancel. Renews automatically every , unless you decide to cancel. You can cancel your subscription at any time.

You can pay with non-card methods if you subscribe for **12 months**.

Please leave your contact phone number here..

We will reach you soon by Whatsapp at the tel number you provide.

Please enter phone number.

**You have subscribed to this plan already!**

Never miss what's happening on Penana!

Turn on notifications

Later

##### Interface Language:

 English 中文

##### Story Language:

 English Chinese (中文)  Indonesian (Bahasa Indonesia)  Malay (Bahasa Melayu)  Tagalog  Vietnamese (tiếng Việt)  German (Deutsch)  Spanish (Español)  French (Français)  Italian (Italiano) Other 

Update
